all-the-jobs.com 2015-11-07

# Privacy Policy / Home | All the Jobs

Allthejobs Limited which incorporates the All-The-Jobs Websites “Allthejobs” is committed to safeguarding and protecting the privacy of the Users of our Website. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that You provide to us, or that we collect from You when you visit our Website so that You can clearly understand our data, security practices, policies and so that You can be assured that Your personal data will only be used in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy describes the types of Personal Information and data we collect, how we use it and who we share it with.  You have choices that You can make about our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information and data. "Personal Information" refers to data information that personally identifies You, such as Your name, address, telephone number and email address. We will also explain how we endeavour to protect the security of Your Personal Information and how You can contact us about our treatment of Your Personal Information.

This Privacy Policy incorporates by reference our Terms and Conditions on the Website which apply to this Privacy Policy. When You access or register to use the Allthejobs Website and provide us with Your Personal Information, it indicates that You accept and consent to our use and disclosure of the information and also data we automatically collect or receive as described in this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy is effective as of 31st July 2013 and may be amended from time to time and updated on this page if we make changes in our data practices and therefore You should check this page from time to time to ensure that You are happy with any changes.

 **What Information Do We Collect?**

We may obtain information about You from various sources, including our Websites, when You register to use the Website or email us or communicate with us in any other way. We also may obtain information about You from business partners, other third parties and publicly available information.

We may obtain various types of information including but not limited to:

  * Your Personal Information, if You choose to provide it voluntarily or if we obtain it from other sources mentioned above. You do not have to give us any Personal Information in order to perform job searches on the Website or to read certain other parts of content on the Website.
  * Your Job search behaviour and preferences. We may use a record of the searches that You make on our Website in order to present You with job recommendations based on Your interests as expressed through Your previous searches.
  * Other details that You may voluntarily submit to us or that may be included in the information provided to us by third parties.
  * If You visit our Website we may collect certain information by automated means, using cookies as described in more detail below. This may include information about our Users devices and how they access the Internet (such as the IP address and the device, browser and operating system type), referral source, URLs that Users exit to once they leave our Website, the dates and times of the visits to our website, information on actions taken on our Website e.g. number of page views, site navigation patterns and job views or application activity, geographical location information e.g. country, state and city from where a User accesses our Website and the types of search terms Users enter to access our Website.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

We may use the information we obtain about You to understand Your needs and personalise Your experience, to improve our website, improve customer service, send periodic emails to You about our Services  and in particular to:

  * Register, manage and maintain your Account.
  * Provide information to You and Services that You request..
  * Maintain a record of the jobs You view or apply to on our Website.
  * Inform You of relevant job postings that may be of interest to You.
  * Provide administrative notices or communications applicable to Your use of the Website.
  * Respond to Your questions and comments and provide customer support.
  * Contact You and deliver information to You that may be targeted to your interests (such as relevant services, educational or other career development opportunities); enable You to communicate with us and solicit Your feedback and input. These communications will contain links for preference management and, where appropriate, unsubscribe links should You decide You do not want to receive further communications.
  * Inform You of changes to our Website and Services.
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business and our Services to You.
  * Analyse and enhance our marketing communications and strategies (including by identifying when emails we have sent to You have been received and read).
  * Analyse trends and statistics regarding Users access to our Website and the jobs viewed.

**Disclosures**

We may disclose information about You for reasons set out in this Privacy Policy and we may also disclose information about You to the extent that we  are required to do so by law and/or in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings and in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights, to enforce our Website Terms and Conditions (including providing information to others for the purpose of fraud prevention, unauthorised transactions, claims and other liabilities, and manage risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorised Users).

 **Administration**

We may also use non-personally identifiable information and certain technical information about Your computer and Your access of the Website (including your IP address) in order to operate, maintain and manage the Website. We collect this information by automated means, using cookies as described in more detail below.

If we seek to use the information we obtain about you in any other ways, we will provide specific notice and request your consent at the time of collection.

 **What Information Do We Share?**

When you click on a Job extract through our Website and then provide any personal information to that Employer/Recruiter/Advertiser they will then have access to information about You and Your potential interest in employment opportunities. Those Employers may use your information to contact you directly. The information supplied by You may become part of the Employer’s database. The use of that Personal Information by the Employer/Recruiter/Advertiser  will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, and we are not responsible for that company’s use of that personal information. We will not share with any Employer/Recruiter/Advertiser the Personal Information that You supply to us on our Website.

We may combine certain non-personally identifiable aggregate data about our Users and use such anonymous aggregate data to prepare reports for Employers/Recruiters. "Aggregate Data" is the demographic information (such as zip code, age, gender, race or ethnicity) and employment information (such as occupation, job title, education and experience) of many individuals that is combined together. Aggregate data is used to analyse the characteristics of various populations and does not identify any specific individuals. Any reports sold by us containing aggregate data cannot be used to identify any individuals.

We may share Personal Information with our service providers who help us in the delivery of our Services to You. These companies may only use or disclose the information as necessary to perform Services on our behalf or as otherwise required by law.

Allthejobs may disclose specific User information when we determine, in good faith, that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, to cooperate with or seek assistance from law enforcement, to prevent a crime or protect national security, or to protect the interests or safety of Allthejobs or other Users of the Website.

The Personal Information we have collected may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership or assets or a bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization of Allthejobs.

 **Cookies and Third Party Advertisers**

A “cookie" is a small text file that websites send to a computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the User’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. The use of cookies allows us to monitor the behaviour of the User visiting the Web site or sending the e-mail.

Allthejobs uses cookies and other similar technologies for the convenience of our Users because they help us to provide You with a better Website by enabling us to monitor which pages You find useful and those which You do not. We can gather Information about Your general internet use e.g the history of jobs reviewed and the job searches conducted by Your computer. When used, these cookies are downloaded onto Your computer’s hard drive but such Information does not identify You personally. It is non-personal statistical data which simply identifies information about You. If we have this Information we can provide you with job recommendations based on your interests as expressed previously through your searches and the web application can tailor its operation to Your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering information about Your preferences. Cookies allow us to ensure our Website functions efficiently and they enable us to serve secure pages to our Users without asking them to sign in repeatedly.  

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most internet browsers allow You to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, You should be aware that some Allthejobs Website features or Services may not function properly without cookies.

 Allthejobs permits third party cookies on its Website. We may uses web analytics services provided by third parties, which use cookies to collect non-personal information about details of our Users’ visits to the Website (including IP addresses) and the resources they access on the Website. These third party web analytics services provide us with reports based on this information in order to help us understand and analyse web page traffic and how Users engage with the Website and tailor it to the User’s needs.

We use third-party advertising companies who may place or access cookies on your computer hard drive when You click on their adverts to distinguish Your web browser uniquely and to keep track of information relating to serving ads on Your web browser, such as the type of ads shown and the webs pages on which the ads appeared. These companies may use information about Your visits to these websites and to other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to You on our Website or on other, third party websites. We also may give third party advertisers the ability to tailor their advertisements on our Website using demographic and preference information we provide to them in aggregate form. This information does not identify You individually. These companies operate under their own privacy policies and Allthejobs encourages you to be aware of the privacy policies of such companies. Allthejobs does not have control over or access to any information contained in the cookies that are set on your computer by third party advertisers.

 **How You Can Update and Control Your Account Information**

You may access, update and amend Personal Information included in Your Account at any time by logging into Your Account and making the necessary changes.

 **Links to Other Websites**

We may allow links to other websites from our Website for your convenience and information. These websites may be operated by companies not owned by Allthejobs. Allthejobs is not responsible for the content of any websites not owned by Allthejobs or their privacy policies.  If you choose to visit these websites You should review their own privacy policies to ensure that You are happy with their practices.

 **Storing and Transferring Your Information and Data**

Allthejobs may transfer, process and store the Personal information and other data we hold about You outside of the country in which you are located, including the United States and Europe. The countries in which we process the Information may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you are located. You agree to this transfer, storing and processing procedure when You provide Your Personal Information to us.

We will do our utmost to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. Users with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should contact Allthejobs by emailing us at info@all-the-jobs.com or by letter to Customer Services at Allthejobs Limited, PO Box 461, SUTTON, SM1 9NN, UK. Please include your name and email address in email requests, and your name and postal address in mail requests.

 **How Do We Protect Your Personal Information?**

In order to protect Your Personal Information from accidental, unlawful or unauthorised destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use, Allthejobs maintains technical, electronic, administrative and physical safeguards to protect and secure that Information.

We do our utmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure your Personal Information and data is stored securely. However, please note the Internet and the electronic transmission of information can never be entirely secure. We cannot guarantee that the security measures we have in place to safeguard Personal Information will never be defeated or fail, or that those measures will always be sufficient or effective. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we cannot guarantee that Your Personal Information will always remain confidential. You understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your conduct and use of the Website and the information You send us electronically or otherwise which you post to the Website.

You will have an Account accessed via your personal email address and You should not share that information with anyone. 

 **Children’s Privacy**

Our Website is not intended to be used by anyone under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not use our Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.

 **Access to Information**

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a small fee to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information. Our data protection registration number is ZA013387.

 **Law**

This policy is governed by the laws of England and Wales. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under this policy shall lie exclusively with the English courts. If any provision of this policy is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of all or part of a provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining parts and provisions of this policy which shall remain in full force and effect.

 **How to Contact Us**

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of Your Personal Information please contact us by emailing us at info@all-the-jobs.com or by letter to Customer Services at Allthejobs Limited, PO Box 461, SUTTON, SM1 9NN, UK. Please include your name and email address in email requests, and your name and postal address in mail requests.

Updated 31st July 2013
